let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the code between the curly braces?",
    answer: "block",
    options: [
      "function",
      "section",
      "body",
      "block"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the value of arr[1].length in following array  -   int[][] arr = {{1,2,3,4,5},{6,7,8,9,10}};",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "10",
      "1",
      "undefined"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the difference between char and Character?",
    answer: "char is a primitive type and Character is a class",
    options: [
      "char is a primitive type and Character is a class",
      "there is no difference, they are both primitive types",
      "char is a class and Character is a primitive type",
      "there is no difference, they are both classes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What class do all Java classes inherit from?",
    answer: "Object",
    options: [
      "Object",
      "List",
      "runtime",
      "collection"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What guarantees type-safety in a collection? " ,
    answer: "Generics",
    options: [
      "Generics",
      "Abstract classes",
      "Interfaces",
      "Collection"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "HashSet internally uses?",
    answer: "Set",
    options: [
      "Set",
      "HashMap",
      "List",
      "Collection"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The most used interfaces from the collection framework are?",
    answer: "Map",
    options: [
      "List",
      "Map",
      "Set",
      "Hash"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The root interface of Java collection framework hierarchy is â€“",
    answer: "List/Set",
    options: [
      "Collection",
      "Root",
      "Collections",
      "List/Set"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of those is synchronized?",
    answer: "Vector",
    options: [
      "ArrayList",
      "LinkedList",
      "Vector",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "ArrayList implements that of the following?",
    answer: "All of these",
    options: [
      "List",
      "RandomAccess",
      "Cloneable",
      "All of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of those permits the storage of the many null values?",
    answer: "All of these",
    options: [
      "Set",
      "List",
      "None of these",
      "All of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "HashSet internally uses?",
    answer: "Set",
    options: [
      "Set",
      "HashMap",
      "List",
      "Collection"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "nextIndex() and previousIndex() are methods of which interface?",
    answer: "Iterator",
    options: [
      "IndexIterator",
      "Iterator",
      "ListIterator",
      "NextPreviousIterator"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Vector extends that of these?",
    answer: "AbstractList",
    options: [
      "ArrayList",
      "LinkedList",
      "AbstractList",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Complexity of ArrayList get method",
    answer: "O(1)",
    options: [
      "O(n-1)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(1)",
      "O(2n)"
    ]
  },


  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];